pansoft.com 2011-10-25

# Pansoft Company Limited

| 

 Privacy Policy

Pansoft Company Limited("Pansoft" or "we" ) respects and protects your privacy. This policy lets you know how we collect and use your personal information, and how you can control its use.

##### Collection and use of personal information

As a visitor to this Web site, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. Some portions of this Web site may require you to give us personally identifiable information, which is information that enables us to identify you, such as your name, email or other address. It is optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to do, however, our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience easier. However, privacy is very important to us. We recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to protecting your privacy. We will not give, loan, or sell any personally identifiable information to any third party, unless legally required to do so. We may store and process personal information to better understand your needs. In addition we may use the information to contact you. If you use this Web site to receive Pansoft's support services, you may be required to supply personal information, and we may use the information in order to perform services to you.

##### Non-personal information

We may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable, such as the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, and the domain name of the Web site from which you linked to our Web site.

##### Protection of your personal information

The importance of security for personal information is of utmost concern to us. Your personal information resides on secure servers and is accessible only to selected Pansoft personnel via password. We use industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, such as firewalls and Secure Socket Layers. We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.

##### Tracking, use of cookies

In order to improve the Web site and provide more convenient, relevant experiences to visitors, this Web site may use "cookies" to track your activities. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card and enables Pansoft to record your passwords and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

While Pansoft uses cookies to track your use of the Site, and web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer, Pansoft does not generally use this information to identify you personally. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.

##### External links

This Web site may contain links to other sites. Pansoft is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

##### Acceptance and changes

By using this Web site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to it, please do not use the Site. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time based on your comments and our need to accurately reflect our data collection and disclosure practices. All changes will become effective immediately and you will not receive notice of these changes. 

##### Privacy complaints

Pansoft takes its users' privacy concerns seriously. If you believe that Pansoft has not complied with this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information, please contact [webmaster@pansoft.com.cn](mailto:webmaster@pansoft.com.cn).  
  
---|---
